Thank you for watching!
Enjoy.
I'm getting pretty good.
I've got a lot of stuff up.
I haven't peeked.
Oh, no.
I can see it now.
Oh, my God.
They've definitely seen us now.
There was a little girl.
Slow down. Don't let them find out.
I saw her. I saw her.
I saw it already.
I knew it! I knew it!
She's not here.
I don't know. I don't know.
Yoo-hoo!
Wow.
I found it
It's so big, it's amazing!
Like this
Cute again!
Red is here today!
Amazing!
That's for sure!Indeed.
I've been to these places on my little NuiNui trip.
That's right.
He said it was cute.
I think I'll leave it here today... my personal belongings at the cherry blossom viewing.
Wow! This is what I mean.
So cute!
He's crazy about cherry blossoms.
I'm crazy about cherry blossoms!
Upstairs!
Oh, look at that! Look at this!
Osaka Castle!
Is it that close?
Osaka Castle Hall!
Oh, my God!
Everyone's there.
Where is everybody?
Everyone!
I don't know where they are!
Where is everybody?
Are they eating okonomiyaki?
I like it.
They're here.
Hey!
You haven't noticed.
There's a panda downstairs.
I like it.
Yoo-hoo!
Oh!Oh!
I made a mistake!
Here comes a member!
Yoo-hoo!
Thank you!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Quite a long time!
Yoo-hoo!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
So far away!
Isn't this amazing?
I'm wearing an M714 L4.
What is this?
Oh, my God!
Who is sitting here? Please comment!
L14 in M11.
M10 L16.
M11
That's great!
It's amazing!!!
You can see it from above!
It's lock-on free time today!
Who's going to go?
Your friends.
Hey, guys!
Look up!Look up!
Who are you talking to?
Right here!
Oh, I see.
I wonder if you can see it from up here.
What is it? What is this?
What? What is it?
What? Kissagen?
What?
Kissagen?
Oh, well, it's possible.
Isn't it possible?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Gentlemen, we really love you.
Well, then, gentlemen, we look forward to working with you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I look forward to working with you.
I don't know you anymore.
I don't know anymore
I don't know anymore.
I'm so irrationally mad at you.
Please don't hate me
It's hard to love
I've been to Canaharz.
I went to Kanahaltz.
Wait a minute!
Canahar wait a minuteKanaharu, wait a minute.
Here you go.
I'm going back to my office.
Everyone's gone.
Oh, boy, I found a toy.
Okkun, I found a toy.
I don't know what to do.
We haven't been on the air for 40 minutes.
I was just in the middle of getting dressed when I came out to say hello.
My hair's all in disarray.
What should I do?
I'm sure I can be patient.
I wonder if there's any left.
I don't know. I don't know.
Here you go.
Oh, that's nice.
Are you okay?
Okay, bye.
Put this down.
It's cute.
Shumaroshi?
Yes, sir.
With Sakura-sama.
I'd like to do this.
Delivery was pretty much a tray number.
But more than showing myself
than the stage
More than on stage
More than on stagefrom
I hope you guys don't talk to other girls.
You said "you.
Real sneeze.
I don't come out that cute.
Oh, I'll shadow the shooter
Shake hands
There's a lot of feeling.
I'm getting nervous, man.
I'm getting a little nervous.
Did you get nervous last night?
You'll be in the shadows?
Yes, I am.
No, I wasn't.
You weren't.
I wasn't.
So you're okay now?
I'm fine.
Bye. Don't be nervous.
Do I smell nice?
It's good.
You know, you're always...
You're licking me.
It's raining, it's raining, it's burning.
It's like a good lick again.
It's pretty... It's like a goo.
That's seriously embarrassing.
No, no, no, no, no.
There you go.
Oh, it smells so good.Oh, it smells so good.
But once it starts, it's over in the blink of an eye.
Two consecutive days of live performances!
Today is the Chotokimeki Advertising Department Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023
Thank you very much for coming to the cute, cute, too cute!
I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa, aka Hiyori of Chotokimeki Green.
Thank you very much. Before the show begins, I would like to give you a few words of caution and a request.
Please refrain from taking pictures, recording, or recording the performance except during the "lock-on free time".
This performance is also for cheering in your seats.
There is no limit to the amount of time or size of your voice on your seat.
Please refrain from shouting that may disturb the performance or cause inconvenience to other audience members.
Excessive jumping is also prohibited.
Seated audience members are not allowed to stand up to watch the performance.
Please be aware that any behavior that may cause inconvenience to other patrons is prohibited.
In case of emergency, please follow the instructions of our staff and evacuate the venue.
You've grown up, you've grown up, you've grown up, Hiyori!
I've listened to your performances maybe six times, so I've got good input and I'm doing great.
Thank you, everyone, and let's get excited for the Osaka show!
Let's have a great time in Osaka!
Thank you very much!
Kanami, Julian, Toka, Hurt, Aki, Heali
Super thrilling publicity department rock on!
Oh, there they are.
Yay!
Oh, here they come.
You weren't idle just now.
And the one in the corner.
Here?
Thank you.Thank you.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Everybody, everybody.
I smell all kinds of perfume.
Oh, wait a minute, I tutted!
You kissed her?
I smell all kinds of perfume.
Did you kiss her?
Wait, wait, did you kiss her?
I'm here. I'm here! I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Oh, forget it!
I'll look around with you!
Let's go, I'm going!
I'm safe. I had a shot. I'm halfway there.
I have a light.
I'm still a little bitty.
Bye bye!
Thank you for a wonderful time in Osaka!
Have fun!
Thanks for all your hard work
I came too close
It's over!
a little bit here
Thank you very much.
We're done.
Thank you. That was fun.
There was a rice tube. He said you had a rice tube.
I'm not making fun of you. You're not.I'm not mocking you. You didn't.
You didn't.
I'm surprised.
I'm surprised at you.
What?
You kissed me again.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
Karamayji. It's not looking good for you, is it?
I like the timing.
It's around the chu...
Oh, no.
I don't know, one of the girls next to me didn't look at me at all.
I thought maybe he was asking me to kiss him.
Of course not.
Why would I think that?
So, I kinda, you know, put my lips out.
I came closer.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was Osaka, wasn't it?
The venue was really hot.
I could hear a lot of voices.
The venue in Osaka was huge.
It was huge.
The level of cheering was like "gogo-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-n".
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Actually, it's half over.
Sixth time today?
Six.Sixth time.
Six times today.
Only four more to go.
I guess I made it back.
Oh no.
This is bad.
Shocking.
I heard about the new announcement today.
How was it?
Asha.
So now everyone can see Asha solo.
I'm sure everyone can see Asha as a whole,
We want to go out and see the posters.
I want to go.
It seems there are a lot of posters.
There were only spare posters.
Spare" is easy to write.
Here they are.
Thank you.
So, the next show will be in Niigata.
Yay!
Everyone's eyes are on us.
It's been a while since I've been there, and probably the first time I've been there as a one-man show.
First time.
It's the first time, isn't it?
It's the first time.
But it's the first time.
Souled Out?
Yes.
So, Sunday at 2:00?
Yes, that's right.Yes.
Yes.
But,
Except for "atseye".
I see.
Indonesia.
Samasteh...
Yes, there is.
Like a special one-man show.
Yes, there's also TGC and so on.
Yes.
Toki-chan, summer is not over yet, is it?
Yes, it is.
Don't be sad. We'll always be here.
We'll always be here.
That's right.
Don't lose everyone.
We're still here.
What do you think?
Autumn went, too.
Only Autumn.
Forgive me!
See you at the next show in Niigata!
I'll be waiting for you!
Thank you very much!
Have a good rest.
Bye-bye!
Bye bye!
I don't know why, but when I laugh, it sure makes the world seem to glow.I don't know why, but when I smile, it's as if the world is shining.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted and blotted out
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the streets turn color
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!